<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Career Quest</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_career">Career</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_softskill">Soft Skill</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="get_started_using_our_apps">Get Started Using our Apps</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account_sign_up_here">Don\'t have an account? Sign Up here</string>
    <string name="google_sign_in">Google Sign-In</string>
    <string name="or_login_using_other_method">Or Login using other method</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="show_hide_password">Show/Hide Password</string>
    <string name="password">PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="username">USERNAME</string>
    <string name="sign_in_to_continue">SIGN IN TO CONTINUE</string>
    <string name="create_an_account">Create an Account</string>
    <string name="email">EMAIL</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="or_sign_up_using_other_method">Or Sign Up using other method</string>
    <string name="google_sign_up">Google Sign-Up</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account_sign_in_here">Already have an account? Sign In here</string>
    <string name="welcome_user">Welcome, User!</string>
    <string name="cari_rekomendasi_mu">Cari Rekomendasi Mu!</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="rekomendasi">Rekomendasi</string>
    <string name="event_picture" />
    <string name="event_title" />
    <string name="stats">Stats</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="general_settings">General Settings</string>
    <string name="carerposibillity">Career Possibility</string>
    <string name="article_detail">detail artikel</string>
    <string name="article_title">judul artikel</string>
    <string name="author">author</string>
    <string name="date">date</string>
    <string name="content_description_media" />
    <string name="description" />
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="send_requests">Send Requests</string>
    <string name="old_password">Old Password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_change">Confirm Change</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter Your Email</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_title">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="reset_password_title">Reset Password Request</string>
    <string name="old_password_fill">Please Input Your Old Password</string>
    <string name="email_requests_fill">Masukkan Email anda yang terdaftar</string>
    <string name="email_empty_warning">Please enter your email address.</string>
    <string name="email_sent_success">Password reset email sent successfully!</string>
    <string name="change_password_fill">Please Input Minimum 8 Characters </string>
    <string name="no_data_available">Tidak ada Hasil</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_fill">Terms and Conditions\n\
        Welcome to CaQu! \n\
        By accessing or using this application, you agree to adhere to the terms and conditions outlined here. Please ensure that you read and understand these terms before using the app. If you do not agree with these terms, you should discontinue using the application immediately. \n\
        1. Acceptance of Terms\n\
        Using CaQu signifies your acceptance of these terms and conditions. The app is intended for high school and vocational school graduates who are exploring career options. You affirm that you are at least 17 years old or have obtained parental or guardian consent. Any information you provide must be accurate and up-to-date to ensure proper functionality and reliable recommendations.\n\

        2. Features of CaQu\n\
        CaQu is designed to assist users in exploring potential career paths based on their skills, academic performance, and interests. The app includes a competency quiz to evaluate your abilities, which serves as a foundation for generating personalized career recommendations. The insights provided are meant to guide you in making informed decisions about your future.\n\

        3. User Responsibilities\n\
        As a user, you are expected to use CaQu responsibly and ethically. You must provide honest information, especially during quizzes, as this data directly influences the recommendations provided. Any misuse of the application, including activities that could harm the platform or other users, is strictly prohibited.\n\

        4. Privacy and Data Use\n\
        Your privacy is our priority. By using CaQu, you consent to the collection and use of your data as described in our Privacy Policy. This includes storing your quiz results to generate recommendations and using anonymized data to improve app features. We assure you that your personal information will not be shared with third parties without your explicit consent, except where required by law.\n\

        5. Limitation of Liability\n\
        The career recommendations offered by CaQu are for guidance purposes only and do not guarantee specific outcomes or job placements. While we strive to provide accurate and helpful insights, users are encouraged to conduct further research and consult professionals when making significant career decisions.\n\

        6. Prohibited Use\n\
        Any actions that compromise the integrity of the app or its services are prohibited. This includes providing false information, attempting to manipulate the system, reverse engineering the app, or using it for unlawful activities.\n\

        7. Intellectual Property Rights\n\
        The content and functionality of CaQu, including but not limited to text, graphics, logos, and algorithms, are protected by intellectual property laws. Users may not reproduce, distribute, or create derivative works based on the app content without prior written consent from the developers.\n\

        8. Changes to Terms and Conditions\n\
        CaQu reserves the right to modify these terms at any time. If significant changes are made, users will be notified through the app. Continued use of the application after such updates implies acceptance of the new terms.\n\

        9. Termination of Use\n\
        We reserve the right to terminate or restrict access to CaQu for users who fail to comply with these terms or engage in activities that harm the app or its users.\n\

        10. Governing Law\n\
        These terms and conditions are governed by the laws of [Your Country/Region], and any disputes will be resolved in accordance with those laws.\n\

        Contact Information\n\
        If you have any questions or concerns about these terms and conditions, please contact us at support@caqu.com.\n\
        \n\Thank you for choosing CaQu to support your career exploration journey!
    </string>
    <string name="subtitle_title">CAPAI CITA CITA!</string>
    <string name="this_is_the_content_of_the_subtitle_section">Temukan minat kalian, \nterus berusaha untuk \nmencapai masa depan cerah impian kalian!</string>
    <string name="ayo_kejar_mimpimu">Ayo kejar mimpimu!</string>
    <string name="halo_user">Halo, User!</string>
    <string name="halo">Halo, %s!</string>
    <string name="banner">banner\n</string>
    <string name="soft_skills">Soft Skills</string>
    <string name="history_image">History Image</string>
    <string name="history_title">History Title</string>
    <string name="grade">Grade</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>
    <string name="toolbar_background" />
    <string name="password_requests_fill">Masukkan Password Baru Anda</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="email_not_found">Email not found</string>
    <string name="network_error">Network error, please try again</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="career_recommendation_title">Rekomendasi Karir</string>
    <string name="no_recommendation">Tidak ada rekomendasi tersedia</string>
    <string name="lanjut">Lanjut</string>
    <string name="career_image" />

</resources>